My name is Danny McNamara.
When I left the FBI,
I thought my crime-fighting
days were over, but then
I learned that terrorist
Karim Farouk was on
the hunt for Cleopatra,
one of the world's most
valuable treasures,
lost for over 2,000 years,
to use her as part of a
massive terror attack.
To find him, I needed some help,
so I went to Lexi Vaziri, a thief.
Excuse me, a master thief.
And my father was killed by Farouk.
Lexi and I have a complicated past.
He wants to bring Farouk
to justice, I want revenge.
Also, there's a mysterious group
who want Cleopatra as much as we do.
We're not sure whether
they're good or bad,
but the one thing we all agree on...
Is that we need to find Cleopatra...
Before Farouk does.
Previously on Blood & Treasure...
Fabi...
You're not lurking
down here in a ski mask
working for the Carabinieri.
You're in the Brotherhood of Serapis.
We will hunt down Farouk
and we kill him, and you, Lexi,
- can be a part of it.
- I can't do this
without Danny, and he's
definitely gonna want
to know who we're working for and why.
And if you tell him,
you will both be dead.
Welcome to La Casa de Chuck.
Maybe it's not such a good idea
if you guys both stay here.
A man named Carlo Velardi runs
the black market bazaar in Rome.
Don't become my problem.
I wouldn't have minded a heads-up
that we were meeting with the Mafia.
The mole in Egyptian intelligence?
Sharif Ghazal.
Ghazal has a file in his
safe with Farouk's network.
I found a letter from
Farouk to my father.
It implies my dad helped fund
his terror operation.
I'm going to receive
the only existing copy
of the track logs from the Sauber Depot
dating back all the way
to the Allied bombings.
Now, you said the sarcophagus
was taken by train from there.
This could be the key
to finding Cleopatra.
_
Our mission to bring Cleopatra
to the Fatherland is doomed.
We need to cut our losses now.
Colonel Steiner is dead.
We need to get rid of that coffin.
We cannot doubt the mission.
The Egyptian queen is our weapon.
She's cursed.
Let's sell her and get
the hell out of Europe.
I am your superior officer.
Our orders are to deliver
Cleopatra to the U-boat
at the port of Huelva.
We either die with the
mummy or live without her.
We swore to protect her.
Even against your brothers?
- Synced and corrected by medvidecek007 -
- www.addic7ed.com -
_
When did you become a vampire?
Sorry, did I wake you?
Nah, nah.
I always like to squeeze in a couple
of confessions before morning mass.
Who goes to confession at dawn?
Old ladies.
They travel in packs.
Those papers for your scrapbook?
Yeah.
It's all lies.
The convoy was hit by Farouk
after the handover ceremony.
He killed the security
team, took the relics.
Probably selling them as we speak.
Killed another two people
to get the transit logs
from Castle Schädelberg
of where the Nazis took Cleopatra.
Now he's flush with cash
and has the inside track
on completing whatever his plan is.
Somebody's got to stop guys like Farouk.
That's what you're doing.
Which is why I'm letting
you stay here rent-free.
Everything balances out.
You have got to start kicking in
for groceries, though.
Lexi has massacred my fridge.
Also, why is she getting
shady packages delivered here?
Yeah, uh, well, since you
won't let her stay here,
her living situation's been in flux.
What does that even mean?
Lexi?
Erica.
Hello.
You break into my place, eat my food,
sleep on my couch, and you're
the one pulling a knife.
Ah, come on. I thought you were out.
And that makes it cool that
you're breaking and entering.
I didn't break anything.
It's just more like
entering and napping.
I have a tiny favor to ask.
Of course you do.
This is a letter...
To my dad... from Karim Farouk.
Didn't your dad work with
the FBI to catch him?
This was dated a year before that.
From the part I can make out,
it sort of implies that they had
a long and fruitful relationship.
Let me guess, you want me to clean it up
so you can read the
rest of what it says.
Well, you are the best
art restorer in the world.
And between you crashing on my couch
and being overly complimentary,
I assume you have no money.
I count my wealth in
the friendships I have.
No, I can't pay you.
I need to know, Erica...
If my dad was working with a terrorist.
You've thrown a lot of business my way,
so I'll give this one
to you on the house.
But it's gonna take some time.
Time you will spend
sleeping somewhere else.
Understood.
Thanks.
Keep digging.
The train can't be much deeper.
Señor Omar, over here!
Is it Cleopatra? Is it?
These are Moroccan uniforms.
I want the train! I want Cleopatra!
Farouk is not a patient man...
And neither am I.
Where are the Nazis?
Keep digging.
Where are you going?
We're not done yet.
Oh, yes, everybody's done.
Do you know who I am?
I think the ignorance is mutual.
I am Carlo Velardi.
My family has controlled
the blood antiquities trade
in Europe for generations.
No one even rents a shovel
in this part of the world
without paying us protection.
My son, he's a...
Come si dice, a young hothead.
I, however, understand
this is just business.
Simple choice.
You pay what you owe
and your dig proceeds.
And if I don't?
Then you discover that my
men have surrounded you.
And we water the ground
with each other's blood.
I'll see that you have your
money first thing tomorrow.
A presto, amico.
_
Any luck?
I make my own luck, Danny.
Oh, so you found something.
No.
What are you guys talking about?
She's trying to find a place to crash.
Just for a few nights, I...
I'm a really considerate roommate.
So she can laugh.
Good to know.
Any progress on following
the money to Farouk
by tracking who the Egyptian
artifacts were sold to?
How many people in
the world do you think
have the lack of scruples,
cash on hand,
and love of Egyptian antiquities
to buy them from a known terrorist?
Can't be this guy because
he's under indictment.
And this one's going
through a messy divorce
and isn't flush with cash.
Now, I'm working on tracking
down these two guys.
What?
Is that Serbian?
Yeah, I think so.
My Serbian isn't great,
but she's saying something
about "him getting a win"
while "she takes a hit."
Hopefully that isn't an assassination
being planned on my phone.
Just spoke to this guy.
Petre Novic. Old friend. Don't ask.
Anyway, he was the second-highest bidder
at a recent underground auction
for items pertaining to Cleopatra.
He was so pissed at being outbid,
he was practically begging
to rat out the winner.
Jessica Wong.
Chinese billionaire living in London.
Also having a black-tie party tonight
to show off her art collection.
Can Interpol get a warrant
to seize her records?
I can try, but it will be
difficult off hearsay
from a conversation
between two criminals.
Danny,
I could use your help.
Lexi.
They won't be able to get the warrant.
You need to go to that party tonight.
Get documentation on the sale.
Anything that can lead
us back to Farouk.
So, you're talking to me
now as a Brotherhood agent,
not the Carabinieri?
Well, generally speaking,
what works for one
works also for the other.
The Brotherhood has
intercepted some chatter,
believed to be from Farouk's group,
indicating that they are very
close to finding Cleopatra.
We need to find out where
they're digging in Europe.
But be careful.
Jessica Wong is not
some rich dilettante.
She's very dangerous.
We had an asset in her place once,
on a different mission.
The asset was apparently discovered
and never heard from again.
And you want me to go in tonight
because I'm expendable?
_
Okay, let's go over our cover.
Again?
Danny, you know I lie for a living?
Yeah, well, I don't.
Humor me.
We're here to buy a
statue for Jacob Reece.
You're Jack Stone,
his antiquities expert,
and I'm his art broker,
Winifred DeMontague.
I swear.
Do you read romance novels
when I'm not looking?
Those are real names of people
that work for Reece, in case she checks.
She'll have someone show you
the provenance for the piece.
Now, while I distract Jessica,
you get ahold of her financial records.
We got to find a link
from her to Farouk.
And then we put her in jail.
Well, I must be rubbing off on you.
You never cared about stopping
the blood antiquities trade before.
I couldn't care less about that.
I just want to punch her
in her stupid, entitled, rich-girl face.
To be fair, she is a
self-made billionaire CEO,
accomplished author, and philanthropist.
She sounds intolerable.
It's like a gilded dollhouse.
We have incoming.
Try to hold off on that face punching.
- No promises.
- Ms. Wong.
Such... a pleasure. Jack Stone.
I work with Mr. Reece's museum in Rome.
Yes. Jay said you're
the most knowledgeable
antiquities expert he's ever known.
I've been looking
forward to meeting you.
And this is Winifred DeMontague.
She'll be assessing the provenance
on the draped kouros.
Assuming everything is in order.
You'll find it impeccable.
My assistant will show you the way.
You know, I do have a fine
Makron in my collection.
It's a fragment of an
Olympian statue in marble.
Is this a test?
Whatever could you mean?
I mean that Makron did
a number of Olympians,
but they were all on the sides of urns
because he was a painter...
Not a sculptor.
Would you like some champagne?
I think you and I are going to
be very good friends, Mr. Stone.
I thought I recognized a familiar face.
Give us a sec, will you?
Simon. Hardwick.
I'm an old friend of Danny McNamara's.
Well, I say old friend. We
met each other once or twice.
Does Jessica know...
That he used to work for the FBI?
FBI? Quite a story.
Yes, and she'd be very
upset if she knew.
Which reminds me, last time I saw you
was in Rome.
Carlo Velardi's soirée...
Or should I say black market bazaar...
Where I chose not to reveal
Mr. McNamara's former
employment because...
He saved my life once...
And I owed him.
But today's a new day, isn't it?
Would you...
Care to join me outside on the terrace?
Ancient Greek.
Dynastic Chinese.
Mayan.
Celtic.
Well, it's clear that
your collection is...
Unified by one shared quality.
Every item is unique.
Like this Makron vase...
It's signed by him.
The only one of its kind.
So I passed another test?
And why would I need to test you?
Well, you put yourself through college
playing in an underground poker game.
I'm guessing old habits die hard.
Does Mr. Reece keep a dossier on me?
Just read your profile in Wired.
Preparation for our negotiation?
Total coincidence.
I was looking for
recommendations on a new TV.
You'll have to excuse me.
You know, Simon,
charming though you are, I must admit,
you have me at a disadvantage.
Well, I was going to
introduce myself in Rome,
but, alas, the place was
raided by the Carabinieri
- and I had to make a hasty exit.
- What a shame.
Indeed, it was.
Actually, on that point,
Carlo's a bit miffed.
Mm. He's under the impression
that you and Mr. McNamara
tipped off the police.
Now, I could always offer
to smooth things over
between the three of you?
You haven't even asked
for anything in return.
The thought of a quid pro
quo had occurred to me.
I hope that's not a euphemism.
Ah. Sweetheart, don't be coy,
or nobody's gonna find Cleopatra.
- What are you on about?
- I know all the players.
Karim Farouk.
The Brotherhood of Serapis.
And you and the Boy Scout in there.
To be fair, you and Mr. McNamara...
My dark horse bet in the race,
and I could make you
the frontrunner for a...
- Oh?
- Reasonable cut.
- Really?
- Let's say three-way split?
Well, watch out. Here comes Curly.
I have everything ready for you.
Wonderful.
Call me when you know something I don't.
Here's something for free.
Try Jessica's desk.
Like me, it's surprising.
I trust the papers are in order?
Do you have provenance
on the Phidian kouros?
I was only told to prepare
the documents for the draped kouros.
And the Phidian kouros.
We're looking at both.
My apologies.
I'll be back in a moment.
Jack.
Is everything okay?
Nice to meet you, Lexi Vaziri.
I trust you've met
Mr. Danny McNamara, formerly of the FBI.
Oh...
Why don't you tell me
who you're working for?
Take my phone. Breast pocket.
Call Agent Gwen Karlsson.
She'll confirm that you were identified
as a bidder in an illegal auction
for stolen Egyptian
relics from Karim Farouk.
Then ask her about that
van parked outside.
It's loaded with agents
ready to crash your party
with tear gas and rubber bullets
if they think that our
lives are in danger.
- You're bluffing.
- Oh, we don't bluff.
We're more of a "sure
thing" kind of operation.
We didn't exchange money directly.
I didn't know I was
dealing with a terrorist.
Save it. How'd you pay him?
I was told to purchase some useless land
through a shell company.
Where?
Spain.
The Andalucía mountains.
Wonderful.
Now...
Be a good girl,
and we won't tell Farouk you talked.
Let's get out of here before they
realize there's no van outside.
Well played. Now let's
hurry up and get to Spain.
_
Good news is, Farouk had Wong
purchase thousands of acres,
so he doesn't exactly know
where to look, either.
Maybe some of these locals
can tell us something here.
Hey, look at this.
"The Ghost Train of Sierra Perdida."
Looks like a tourist trap.
It's a real local legend from 1944.
Train came out of nowhere
and then disappeared.
Jessica Wong's land
purchase was along the same
railroad tracks that this
ghost train went missing.
And you think it's our lost Nazi train.
Hey. ¿Qué tal?
Hey, how's your Spanish?
Not as good as my Serbian.
Better than my Italian.
Probably as good as my French.
Are those all from ex-boyfriends?
I happen to have a
facility with languages.
Eh, I speak English.
Oh. Great.
We're interested in the Ghost
Train of Sierra Perdida.
Well, I'm afraid I can't help you.
The area is all private property now.
Off-limits.
Ruined my tourism business.
Can you show us where?
The train was last spotted
at this station in Córdoba
but never arrived at this stop.
If the train derailed between stations,
it's possible it's still out there.
How much for the map?
15 euros.
It says five.
It's the last one.
50. 50, not 15.
I'm sorry, my English is not perfect.
I'm just gonna let
you two work this out.
Grab some of these supplies from you?
Oh, these supplies?
Oh, those are very special supplies...
Perfect. No service.
One time I ask for help.
How much for that hat?
One time.
Think I got a pretty
good deal on supplies.
Please tell me you got him
to throw in the hat for free.
Freeish.
And that is what happens when you come
from a culture that doesn't haggle.
Come on. Let's ride.
_
Lexi, bad girl.
Oh, I'm famished.
Got any food in there?
Let's see.
Folding shovels. Binoculars.
Oh, wait.
I think this is actually jerky.
Oh, yes.
Does jerky ever go bad?
What's that sound?
Me complaining.
Farouk's men.
But no Farouk.
They're digging way outside the X-marks.
There's a bridge with a sharp bend
a couple miles from here.
If the train derailed,
it happened there.
"They're digging in the wrong place."
Yeah, that's what I just...
Oh, God, is that from some movie?
Just forget it.
If you explain it to me,
I'll pretend to find it funny.
No, moment's gone.
Ooh.
There.
Mountain pass. Curve in the track.
Steep drop.
I think you're right.
Looks like the perfect spot
for a Nazi train to have
disappeared for 75 years.
Let's go check out what's
in that ravine ahead.
I thought we'd be there by now.
We should have brought way more food.
Huh.
We're officially in
the middle of nowhere.
No way.
- We found it.
Brilliant.
Now let's see if she's inside.
Crate's here, but no Cleopatra.
- Yeah, she's gone.
- Danny.
Free booze.
Absinthe.
Strong absinthe.
Too late again.
I'd say you're right on time.
So, I finally caught up with you.
So, you found her.
We found what's left of a crate
and some old absinthe.
Cleopatra's long gone.
Well, we tried our best.
The adventure continues.
You two destroyed my bazaar,
ruined my reputation.
I lost millions that night,
and now I'm out here like a zoccola,
shaking down treasure hunters
just to make up what I lost.
The people you're dealing with
aren't just treasure hunters.
They're terrorists.
Karim Farouk's people.
The guy who blew up the pyramid?
And that's Omar,
Farouk's right-hand man.
You know, I've been very
much looking forward
to finally killing you.
You're 0 for 2, sport.
Any more jokes?
How about you, Fredo?
Or are you gonna run to Daddy?
- I'm gonna kill you.
- Shh, Luca. Shh.
You know, I really should thank you all.
The only thing my men could dig up
was a hole full of skeletons.
Never would have found this without you.
She's all yours
if you can dig her out of that car.
Fantastic.
I just need two volunteers to help dig.
_
Suspected members of the Brotherhood.
Vaziri.
Fathers and their secrets.
Hey.
Lexi Vaziri.
I need her phone number.
Huh?
Anything yet?
Still digging.
- Oh, come on.
- Just play along.
Found something!
Step aside.
We're coming down.
I need your lucky charm.
Luca, no!
Don't you dare.
Go. Go.
No!
We need to go.
Ever since I met you,
you've done nothing but take from me!
Why are we stopping?
I want to check something out first.
All right, we'd better hurry
and get the hell out of Spain
before Carlo comes looking for us.
Omar mentioned they
found skeletons here.
Got me curious.
Six Nazi uniforms but...
No bodies.
Found 'em.
Why did someone strip
off their uniforms?
Look at the scrap of this insignia.
It's a Casablanca regiment.
What the hell are they doing here?
Moroccan troops were brought in to
quash anti-Franco rebels in 1944.
Hmm.
Nine-millimeter.
A Luger?
We're not far from where
the train derailed.
Shoot-out in the train
for... whatever reason.
Surviving Nazis grab Cleopatra.
They come across these
Moroccans, kill them,
take their uniforms, and
head straight to Morocco.
Best way to get Cleopatra out of Europe.
So they went to Casablanca.
That's what it looks like.
It's the closest and
largest port in Morocco.
Omar had the answer in his hands,
and he didn't even know it.
Ah, but he didn't have a Danny.
Thanks.
Oh, of course.
Now we have reception.
Hey, before we go to Casablanca,
can we stop in Rome?
Sure.
Something wrong?
Farouk's letter to my dad.
I sent it to someone to see
if she could restore it,
maybe help me make some sense of it.
Oh, she find anything?
She won't tell me what
she found over text.
Said it's not safe.
What if it's true?
What if my dad worked with Farouk?
Look, I knew your dad to be a good man.
But whoever he was,
it doesn't define you.
You're the sum of your own choices.
That's not exactly reassuring.
_
Hey.
- You.
You two know each other?
He's tried to arrest
me, like, ten times.
You said you went to a
restorer, not a forger.
Master forger.
Allegedly.
He's not here for you.
You can trust me trusting him.
What'd you find in the letter?
What's it say?
It doesn't matter what it says.
It's as fake as the Botticelli
hanging in the National Gallery.
- I knew it.
- Danny.
Sorry.
I found a sample of Farouk's writing
from an early manifesto.
It's a good forgery,
but the numbers in
the date give it away.
There are ink blots over
the numbers 8 and 9.
Whoever wrote it hesitated
over the curved lines
and pressed the pen too much.
It's called criminal tremor.
Why would someone implicate my father
as having worked with Farouk?
I-I need to get some air.
I thought she'd be happy.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure she
doesn't know how to feel.
If her father was a bad guy,
at least his death wasn't her fault.
I guess those checks won't
stop going out anytime soon.
What checks?
Most of her money goes
to the families affected by
the bombing that killed her father.
I had no idea.
I don't think she wants anyone to know.
I make everything look like
legit insurance payouts
so nobody asks questions.
_
Fabi.
You don't need to announce it
for the whole neighborhood.
Well, you don't need to creep up on me.
If you answered your phone, you'd
know I've been looking for you.
We were in the mountains in Spain.
I didn't have reception.
Found the Nazi train.
Yes, I know.
Interpol is all over
what's going on there.
Agent Karlsson suspects
your involvement,
and she is not pleased.
She wants to bring you
both in for questioning.
You need to plan your
next move carefully, Lexi.
Yeah, well, it's always better to ask
for forgiveness than permission.
When we find Cleopatra,
all will be forgiven.
- So you're close?
- They took it to Casablanca.
Headed out first thing.
Good.
Did you find anything about my dad
in that file I stole in Cairo?
Ghazal had a letter in his vault I...
Forgot to tell you about.
You forgot?
Look, I had to find out for myself.
Someone forged that letter
and made it look like my
dad was working with Farouk.
I've been going through the Farouk file.
The half you were able
to retrieve, anyway.
Your father was the one who originally
found the documents
among Farouk's things.
It seemed he called Ghazal
to confirm something that concerned him.
I think that's what got him killed.
Ghazal tipped off Farouk?
I believe so.
We are monitoring him.
Do not make any hasty moves.
You want to know the
truth about your father,
why he was killed,
trust us.
Trust you...
Must be Danny.
Go.
Hey.
What?
You have more of your dad's
goodness in you than you let on.
He'd be really proud of you.
I've got a lead on a
place to stay tonight.
Gonna go check it out.
Okay.
Well, just in case, I'm
working on a plan B.
Good night.
Y-Y-You won't even notice us.
We're barely in Rome.
But why's it got to be my place?
Hey, "blessed are those
that feed the hungry",
"clothe the naked,
"shelter the homeless..."
You do not want to go toe-to-toe
with me on Bible verses.
Chuck, she's low on funds.
If she has a place to crash
for a night or two,
she doesn't pick the pockets
of the old ladies you
see for confession.
It's a virtuous cycle.
Hmm? Fine.
But she pitches in for chores.
And no walking around naked.
I promise we'll respect your space.
You better.
I'm gonna text her to let her know.
I think she's trying to
find a place as we speak.
How'd you get my number?
Pleased to see you, too.
Jessica Wong's security team
can be quite resourceful,
- when they need to be.
- Ah.
Look, you told me to give you a call
when I knew something that you didn't.
I've been looking into
the Brotherhood for a while.
Came across an old list of names.
Former members at some time or other.
One of the names kind of stuck out.
Vaziri?
I'd say your father
was in the Brotherhood.
What?
My father, Brotherhood, how...
Is that possible?
The Brotherhood holds many secrets.
Who knows what else they're hiding?
- Synced and corrected by medvidecek007 -
- www.addic7ed.com -